Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series I. Sound Recordings (1-24)
  - LPs - SR 260-310 (Box 6)
    - Astrology rap; Star power Performed by: Fredrick Davies and Lewis Anton, 1980; SR-285 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Star Power
      Track listing: Astrology rap -- Star power.
    - Street talk / Madam Rapper Funky constellation (T Osaze, W Eixon, A Mashaa) Performed by: Madam Rapper, 1979; SR-286 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Rota Enterprises
      Track listing: Street talk; Funky constellation (vocal) -- Street talk; Funky constellation (instrumental).
    - Ladies delight Performed by: Mr. Q, ca.1975; SR-287 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Monika's Production
      Track listing: Ladies delight -- Ladies delight (long version).
    - Want the body; The Incredable Fly's rap Performed by: Incredable Fly, 1979; SR-288 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Superfly Music
      Track listing: Want the body -- The Incredable Fly's rap.
    - Das war 1980 Rap / Dr. Misch Performed by: Dr. Misch, ca.1980; SR-289 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Super sound single
    - Cheeba Crew Performed by: Cheeba Crew, ca.1975; SR-290 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Cheeba Crew
    - Ghetto bird / the Plainwrap Band Performed by: Plainwrap, 1983; SR-291 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Marval Records
      Track listing: Vocal -- Instrumental.
    - Invasion from the Planet Detroit Performed by: Planet Detroit, 1984; SR-292 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Pandisc
      Track listing: Invasion from the Planet Detroit (dub mix) -- Invasion from the Planet Detroit (short version).
    - Hard to the body / by Point Blank MCs Performed by: Point Blank M.C.s, ca.1985; SR-293 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Beauty and the Beat; Prod. Duke Bootee for Duke Bootee Productions
      Track listing: Hard to the body. Vocal; Radio edit; Instrumental.
    - Spider / Narada Michael Waldon [sic] [et al] Performed by: Narada Michael Walden, ca.1985; SR-294 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Star Records
    - Rapper's delight = Melô‚ do tagarela: (music taken from "Good times") / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1980; SR-295 (Box 6)
      Publisher: RCA Victor
      Track listing: Long version -- Short version.
    - Intelligence / Monzie-D & Too Quick Performed by: Monzie-D, 1983; SR-296 (Box 6)
      Publisher: BC Records
      Track listing: Intelligence -- Intelligence (Instrumental) -- Intelligence (Short version).
    - 24/24 music / Dinosaur L Performed by: Dinsoaur L, vocal and instrumental ensemble, 1981; SR-297 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Sleeping Bag Records
      Track listing: #1 (you're gonna be lean on your bean) -- #5 (go bang) -- #2 (no, thank you) -- #7 -- #3 (in the corn belt) -- #6 (get set).
    - Calling Doctor Ice; Ice theme / Doctor Ice Performed by: Doctor Ice, 1981; SR-298 (Box 6)
    - You don't really wanna battle; Battle beats Brooklyn style (scratch version); You don't really wanna battle (instrumental) / Cut Master DC Performed by: Cut Master D.C, 1985; SR-299 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Zakia Records
    - That's life / Cut Master DC Performed by: Cut Master D.C, ca.1985; SR-300 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Airport Records
    - Rapper's delight / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-301 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Rapper's delight (14:31) -- Rapper's delight (6:37).
    - It's your rock Performed by: Fantasy Three, 1983; SR-302 (Box 6)
    - Rapper's delight / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-303 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Sugarhill
      Track listing: Rappers delight (long version) -- Rappers delight (short version).
    - 30 days / Run-DMC Performed by: Run-D.M.C, 1984; SR-304 (Box 6)
      Track listing: 30 days -- 30 days (instrumental).
    - It's like that; Sucker MC's Performed by: Run-D.M.C, 1983; SR-305 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Ariola
      Track listing: It's like that -- Sucker M.C.'s (krush-groove 1).
    - Schooling: Put your mind to the message / Sherod Performed by: Sherod, ca.1985; SR-306 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Funk Groove Records; Distributed by Land of Hits
      Track listing: Schooling (vocal) -- Schooling (instrumental).
    - Space cadet; I just had to dance / The Softones Performed by: Softones, ca.1975; SR-307 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Park-Way International Records
    - Party rap / Rhythm Makers Ltd Performed by: Rhythm Makers Ltd, 1983; SR-308 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Star Vision International Records
      Track listing: Party rap -- Party rap (instrumental).
    - Break 4 love / Raze Performed by: Raze, ca.1985; SR-309 (Box 6)
      Publisher: Grove St.
      Track listing: Break 4 love -- Drop the panties -- Instrumental -- Break 4 love -- Spanish fly -- Radio vocals.
    - Win Jesse win / Stack Performed by: Stack, 1984; SR-310 (Box 6)
      Track listing: Win Jesse win (vocal) -- Win Jesse win (instrumental).
  - LPs - SR 311-357 (Box 7)
    - Beat bop Performed by: Rammelzee vs. K-Rob, 1983; SR-311 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Tartown Record Co.
    - Are you ready / TJ Swann; P Mel; Barry B Performed by: TJ Swann, 1981; SR-312 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Express Records
      Track listing: Are you ready -- Are you ready, instrumental part 2.
    - Young ladies Performed by: Lonnie Love, vocals; with vocal and instrumental ensemble, 1981; SR-313 (Box 7)
      Track listing: Young ladies -- Young ladies: instrumental version.
    - You've been hunchin' / La She Ba Performed by: La She Ba, 1981; SR-314 (Box 7)
      Track listing: You've been hunchin' -- You've been hunchin' (instrumental)
    - You can do it / TC & Dangerous Three Performed by: TC& Dangerous Three, 1984; SR-315 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Trasan Records
      Track listing: You can do it -- You can do it (instrumental).
    - Maximus party (deacon) / TJ Swann & Peewee Mel and Swann Controllers Performed by: TJ Swann, ca.1975; SR-316 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Express; Distributed by Apexton
    - Maximus qary (deacon) / TJ Swann & Peewee Mel and Swann Controllers Performed by: TJ Swann, ca.1975; SR-317 (Box 7)
    - Let's do it again; Cosmo rap / Ronnie Jones + Disco Circus Performed by: Ronnie Jones, 1980; SR-318 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Lollipop Records
    - Brave new worlds / Jack Hammer Performed by: Jack Hammer, vocals; with acc, 1966; SR-319 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Distributed in Great Britain by Polydor Records
      Track listing: Brave new world -- Thanks -- Love ladder -- Switch blade operator -- From the womb to the tomb -- Dosby dania amerikanski -- Black snow -- Shut up world -- Down in the subway -- J.C. -- When a girl loves a girl -- Off limits soldier boy.
    - Motor booty affair / Parliament Performed by: Parliament, with accompaniment, 1978; SR-320 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Casablanca
      Track listing: Mr. Wiggles -- Rumpofsteelskin -- (You're a fish and I'm a) Water sign -- Aqua boogie (A psychoalphadiscobetabioaquadoloop) -- One of those funky things -- Liquid sunshine -- The motor-booty affair -- Deep.
    - Adventures of Grandmaster Flash on the wheels of steel Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1981; SR-321 (Box 7)
      Track listing: The adventures of Grandmaster Flash on the wheels of steel -- The adventures of Grandmaster Flash on the wheels of steel (the party mix).
    - Party mix / Grandmaster Flash Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, 1981; SR-322 (Box 7)
    - Rock the message rap / Grand Master Chilly T & Stevie G Back to back / Keeling Beckford Connection Performed by: Grand Master Chilly T, ca.1985; SR-323 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Eclipse Records
    - Positive life / Love Bug Star-Ski & The Harlem World Crew Performed by: Love Bug Star-Ski, 1981; SR-324 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Tay-Ster Records
    - I paid the cost to be the boss / Masterdon Performed by: Masterdon, ca.1985; SR-325 (Box 7)
      Track listing: I paid the cost to be the boss -- I paid the cost to be the boss (instrumental).
    - We are people too / Master Jay Performed by: Master Jay, ca.1985; SR-326 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Heavenly Crown Records
    - Super disco brakes Volume two Performed by: Various performers, ca.1980; SR-327 (Box 7)
      Track listing: Funky drummer (James Brown) -- Catch a groove (Juice) -- Smokin' cheeba cheeba (Harlem Underground Band) -- Use me (Bill Withers) -- Dove (Cymande) -- Watch dog (Ann Winley) -- Sophisticated Cissy (Meters).
    - Teen machine rap / Teen Machine Performed by: Teen Machine, ca.1985; SR-328 (Box 7)
    - Dancing heart / Universal Two Performed by: Universal Two, ca.1985; SR-329 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Golden Flamingo
    - Word em up / T O Vice Performed by: TOVice, ca.1975; SR-330 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Boom City
    - Rapper's nightmare (vocal); Rapper's nightmare (instrumental) / Boss K Performed by: Boss K, ca.1985; SR-331 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Street Jam
    - Wanna groove; Shake together / Kay West Performed by: Kay West, ca.1985; SR-332 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Cat Record
    - Message / Grandmaster Flash & the Furious Five Performed by: Grandmaster Flash, ca.1985; SR-333 (Box 7)
      Publisher: SOS Recording: Marketed & distributed by PRT Records
      Track listing: She's fresh -- It's nasty -- Scorpio -- It's a shame -- Dreamin -- You are -- The message.
    - Games of life; Games of life dub / Just Four Performed by: Just Four, ca.1985; SR-334 (Box 7)
    - Rap-a-reenie / Reen Machine Performed by: Reen Machine, ca.1985; SR-335 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Dir-Tee Records
      Track listing: Rap-a-reenie -- Oo chak-a-willie (X-rated not for air play).
    - To the beat y'all; Loose on forty duce / Sangria Performed by: Sangria, 1981; SR-336 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Real to Reel
    - Rapper's delight / Sugar Hill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-337 (Box 7)
    - Zoot 2 Performed by: Dr. Ice Rap (Kalvin Washington), ca.1980; SR-338 (Box 7)
    - Brer soul / All words and music by Melvin Van Peebles Performed by: Melvin Van Peebles, 1969; SR-339 (disc 1) (Box 7)
      Publisher: A & M Records
      Track listing: Lilly done the Zampoughi everytime I pulled her coattail -- Mirror mirror on the wall -- Coolest place in town -- You can get up before noon without being a square -- The dozens -- Tenth and Greenwich (Women's House of Detention) -- Come raising your leg on me -- Sera sera Jim -- Catch that on the corner.
    - Ain't supposed to die a natural death / Melvin Van Peebles Performed by: Melvin Van Peebles, ca. 1970; SR-339 (disc 2) (Box 7)
      Track listing: Three boxes of longs please -- You ain't no astronaut -- Come on feet do your thing -- Funky girl on motherless Broadway -- Put a curse on you -- I got the blood -- You gotta be holdin' out five dollars on me -- Heh heh (chuckle) good morning sunshine -- Salamaggi's birthday
    - Hustler's convention / Lightnin' Rod Performed by: Lightnin' Rod (i.e. Jalal Udim or Alafia Pudim); with instrumental acc, 1973; SR-340 (Box 7)
      Publisher: United Artists
      Track listing: Sport -- Spoon -- The Cafe Black Rose -- Brother Hominy Grit -- Coppin' some fronts for the set -- Hamhock's hall was big -- The bones fly from Spoon's hand -- The break was so loud, it silenced the crowd -- Four bitches is what I got -- Grit's den -- The shit hits the fan again -- Sentenced to the chair.
    - Call me miss-ter / the Pearl Box Revue Performed by: Pearl Box Revue, ca.1975; SR-341 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Snake Eyes
      Track listing: At the party -- The serious side of us.
    - Rappin black in a white world / the Watts Prophets Performed by: Watts Prophets, with musical accompaniment: Buddy Woodson, bass; Dee Dee McNeil, piano, 1971; SR-342 (Box 7)
      Publisher: ALA
      Track listing: Sell your soul -- Take it -- Instructions -- Amerikkka -- Dem niggers ain't playing -- Pain -- What is a man -- A pimp -- Tenements -- The master -- Ask not -- Freedom flame -- Hello niggers -- There's a difference between a black man and a nigger -- What it is, sister -- Everybody watches -- Watch out black folks -- The prostitute -- Fucked -- Black in a white world -- Angela -- Wake up.
    - Right on! / the original Last Poets Performed by: Last Poets, 1969; SR-343 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Juggernaut
      Track listing: Jibaro/my pretty nigger -- Been done already -- Hey now -- Die nigga!!! -- Un rifle oracion/rifle prayer -- Tell me brother -- Black woman -- James Brown -- Soul -- Today is a killer -- Little Willie Armstrong Jones -- Puerto Rican rhythms -- Poetry is black -- Jazz -- The Shalimar -- Into the streets -- Alley -- The library
    - Betcha got a dude on the side Performed by: Star Quality & Class, ca. 1975; SR-344 (Box 7)
      Publisher: R&R Records
      Track listing: Betcha got a dude on the side (vocal) -- Betcha got a dude on the side (instrumental)
    - Funkbox party (live) Performed by: Masterdon Committee, 1982; SR-345 (Box 7)
      Track listing: Funkbox party (live) (instrumental) -- Funkbox party (live) (vocal)
    - Scoopy rap Performed by: Scoopy, 1980; SR-346 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Sound Around Town
      Track listing: Scoopy rap (vocal) -- Scoopy rap (instrumental)
    - Gangster scene; On your knees Performed by: Sh-Rock and Cut Master Funk (aka H.B.O.) (side A) and L. Springsteen (side B), ca. 1985; SR-347 (Box 7)
      Track listing: A. The gangster scene: 1. club mix -- 2. radio mix -- B. On your knees: 1. vocal mix -- 2. instrumental
    - Spiderap; A Corona jam Performed by: Ron Hunt (side A) and Ronnie G. & The S.M. Crew (side B), 1979; SR-348 (Box 7)
    - Black Super Man: from the south side of Krypton Performed by: Black Super Man, 1981; SR-349 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Sterling Byrd Productions
      Track listing: Premium Black Super Man (from the south side of Krypton) / guest artist: Muhammad Ali; Premium theme from the south side of Krypton
    - Philosophy rappin' spree Performed by: Super 3 (Lorenzo Douglas, Darryl Reid, and David Robinson), 1980; SR-350 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Delmar International Records
    - This is a party; The "micstro" Performed by: Radiance (featuring "Prize" on side A, featuring "R.C." on side B), ca. 1975; SR-351 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Ware Records
    - Jahneen / Gigolette Performed by: Gigolette, 1982; SR-352 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Bexy
    - Doctor Love & Sister Love rap Performed by: Dr. Love & Sister Love, 1980; SR-353 (Box 7)
    - Funk rap Performed by: Ikim & Bacardi, 1980; SR-354 (Box 7)
      Track listing: Funk rap (vocal) --Funk rap (instrumental)
    - We rap more mellow (maxi version) / The Younger Generation Performed by: Younger Generation, features Mellie Mel, Kid Creole, Rahim, Mr. Ness, Cowboy, 1979; SR-355 (Box 7)
      Track listing: We rap more mellow (maxi version) -- We rap more mellow (micro version) -- We rap more mellow (mini version)
    - Lies; Check out the radio Performed by: Spectrum City, 1984; SR-356 (Box 7)
      Publisher: Vanguard
      Track listing: Lies -- Check out the radio (bonus beat) -- Lies (radio edit) -- Lies (dub) -- Check out the radio (bonus beat--dub).
    - Talking and scratching (for the people) Performed by: The Computer People Communicaters (CPC), ca. 1985; SR-357 (Box 7)
      Publisher: ElectricLand Records
      Track listing: Talking and scratching (for the people) (vocal) -- Talking and scratching (for the people) (instrumental)
  - LPs - SR 358-412 (Box 8)
    - Chance Band live Performed by: Chance Band, ca. 1975; SR-358 (Box 8)
      Publisher: S&D Records
      Track listing: Foxy Brown -- Hey la di da di -- Big ole butt -- S.E. boogie -- Mr. "G" in the mix -- Jazz song -- Walk into the gogo -- Displaying
    - Rappin' aint no thing Performed by: Boogie Boys, featuring Kool Ski, Kid Delight, and Disco Dave; music by trazarran band, 1981; SR-359 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Mike and Dave Records
    - Let's start 2 dance again Performed by: Bohannon; with Dr. Perri Johnson, 1981; SR-360 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Unidisc
      Track listing: Let's start II dance again (7:38) -- Let's start II dance again (party version) (7:38).
    - Inhuman orchestra Performed by: Biz Markie and T.J. Swan; produced and mixed by Marley Marl, 1986; SR-361 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Make the music with your mouth Biz -- The Biz dance -- They're coming to take me away ha-haa -- A one, two -- The Biz dance (dub version) -- Make the music with your mouth Biz (instrumental)
    - Got to be in, got to be out Performed by: Ben Crumidy and Bernard Thomas (aka Rapper Dapper), ca. 1985; SR-362 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Got to be in, got to be out -- Got to be in, got to be out (instrumental)
    - Ah-boo; Jungle pack man Performed by: Arthur (Maniac) McCloud and Maxx Kidd, 1982; SR-363 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Bush Record Co.
      Track listing: Ah-boo -- Jungle pack man -- Ah-boo (instrumental) -- Jungle pack man (instrumental)
    - Planet rock Performed by: Soul Sonic Force, 1982; SR-364 (Box 8)
      Publisher: 21 Records
      Track listing: Planet rock (vocal) -- Planet rock (instrumental)
    - Dallas; Nightlife groove Performed by: The Mexicano, B. Bra, 1980; SR-365 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Dallas (full version) / The Mexicano -- Nightlife groove / B. Bra
    - Let's do it Performed by: Jesse Gee, ca. 1985; SR-366 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Sound of the Universe Record Corp.
    - I'm Sue, I'm a goodin Performed by: Sweet Carletta Sue and the Poo Poo Man Saturday Nite Band, ca. 1985; SR-367 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Electric Land Records
      Track listing: I'm Sue, I'm a goodin (uncensored) -- I'm Sue, I'm a goodin (censored, edited version) -- I'm Sue, I'm a goodin (censored, long version)
    - Education wrap Performed by: Community People, 1980; SR-368 (Box 8)
    - Can you do it (Superman); Back to Metropolis Performed by: Dr. Superman and Lady Sweet, 1979; SR-369 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Major Record and Filmworks
      Track listing: Can you do it (Superman) / Dr. Superman n' Lady Sweet -- Back to Metropolis / Dr. Superman
    - Planet rock Performed by: Africa Bambaata and the Soul Sonic Force, 1982; SR-370 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Planet rock (extended version) -- Planet rock (extended instrumental version)
    - She got it like that / Abiodun Performed by: Abiodun Oyewole, 1981; SR-371 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Street Beat
      Track listing: She got it like that --She got it like that (instrumental)
    - Play that beat, Mr. D.J.; Desti-dub; Got a date; The big hurt Performed by: G.L.O.B.E. & Whiz Kid, Two Sisters, Dionne Warwick, and Bare Essence, 1983; SR-372 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Play that beat, Mr. DJ (master mix first place) -- Desti-dub -- Got a date (extended edit) --The big hurt (extended edit)
    - Sugarhill funk Performed by: Furious Five, the Sugarhill Gang, The Sequence, Funky Four + One, Spoonie Gee, West Street Mob, Trouble Funk, and Adventure, 1982; SR-373 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Showdown --Funk a doodle rock jam -- That's the joint -- Monster jam -- Funk box -- Sing a simple song -- Hey fellas -- Phantasy Eyeland (What is your phantasy)
    - Rapper's delight / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-374 (Box 8)
    - Rapper's delight / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-375 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Sugar Hill Records Ltd.
      Track listing: Rapper's delight (long version) -- Rapper's delight (short version).
    - Rapper's delight / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-376 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Sugarhill Records Ltd.
    - Delicias de un charlatan / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1980; SR-377 (Box 8)
      Publisher: RCA
      Track listing: Delicias de un charlatan (Rapper's delight) (long version) -- Delicias de un charlatan (Rapper's delight) (short version).
    - Rapper's delight / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-378 (Box 8)
    - New love rap Performed by: Spoonie Gee, ca. 1975; SR-379 (Box 8)
      Track listing: New love rap (vocal) -- New love rap (instrumental)
    - Summer fun Performed by: Jackie "Small" Cochran, 1980; SR-380 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Summer fun (vocal) -- Summer fun (instrumental)
    - Do it any way you wanna Performed by: Mike T.; with acc, 1981; SR-381 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Golden Pyramid Records
      Track listing: Do it any way you wanna (vocal) -- Do it any way you wanna (club version).
    - Ma quale idea Performed by: Pino D'Angio, 1981; SR-382 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Machine Records
    - Rapper's delight = El cotorreo / Sugarhill Gang Performed by: Sugar Hill Gang, 1979; SR-383 (Box 8)
      Publisher: TreÌbol
      Track listing: El cotorreo (Rapper's delight) (versio´n larga) -- El cotorreo (Rapper's delight) (versio´n corta).
    - Super-Wolf can do it Performed by: Super-Wolf, vocals; with instrumental acc, ca. 1980; SR-384 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Big Bad Records
      Track listing: Super-Wolf can do it -- Anybody can do it
    - Spanglish Performed by: Spanish Fly and the Terrible Two (vocals); accompaniment by Pumpkin and Friends, 1981; SR-385 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Spanglish (vocal) -- Spanglish (instrumental)
    - Uprock / Rock Steady Crew Performed by: Rock Steady Crew, 1984; SR-386 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Virgin Records
      Track listing: Uprock extended version -- Instrumental version -- 7" version
    - Roof is on fire / Rock Master Scott and the Dynamic Three Performed by: Rock Master Scott, 1985; SR-387 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Reality
      Track listing: The roof is on fire -- The roof is on fire (scratchin') -- The roof is on fire (jivin').
    - It's life (you gotta think twice) Performed by: Rock Master Scott and the Dynamic 3, 1983; SR-388 (Box 8)
      Track listing: It's life (you gotta think twice) -- It's life (you gotta think twice) (instrumental) -- It's life (you gotta think twice) (bonus version).
    - Sunshine, partytime; Dubbing in sunshine Performed by: Rockers Revenge; featuring Donnie Calvin, 1982; SR-389 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Street Wise
      Track listing: Sunshine, partytime (rap) -- Dubbing in sunshine.
    - Mirda rock / Reggie Griffin & Technofunk Performed by: Reggie Griffin, 1982; SR-390 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Sweet Mountain
      Track listing: Mirda rock (vocal) -- Mirda rock (instrumental)
    - Razz Performed by: Matt Warren and Ralphi Rosario, 1985; SR-391 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Sunset Records
      Track listing: Pump it up -- Razz-matazz -- Say it -- Kill yourself dancing
    - Raptivity Performed by: Ronnie Gee, 1980; SR-392 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Raptivity -- Raptivity (instrumental)
    - Hip hop beat / the Rapologists Performed by: Rapologists, featuring Flakey "C" and Early Daze (side one) and Master M.C. (side two), ca. 1980; SR-393 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Billy Boy Records
      Track listing: Kids' rap -- Party rap -- Street mix
    - Spoonie is back / Spoonie Gee Performed by: Spoonie Gee, 1981; SR-394 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Spoonie is back (vocal) -- Spoonie is back (instrumental).
    - Monster jam / Spoonie Gee meets the Sequence Performed by: Spoonie Gee, 1980; SR-395 (Box 8)
      Track listing: Monster jam (vocal) -- Monster jam (instrumental).
    - Another one bites the dust Performed by: Sugar Daddy; music by Common Sense, 1980; SR-396 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Roll-Royce
      Track listing: Another one bites the dust (rap) -- Another one bites the dust (instrumental)
    - Another one bites the dust Performed by: Sugar Daddy; music by Common Sense, 1980; SR-397 (Box 8)
      Publisher: One Way Records
    - Preppy rap (Do the alligator) Performed by: Chatsworth & Burt, 1981; SR-398 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Raptile Records
      Track listing: Preppy rap (Do the alligator) -- Preppy rap, part 2 (Do the alligator)
    - Football freaks / Clarence Reid Performed by: Clarence Reid and Happy Stepchild, 1981; SR-399 (Box 8)
      Publisher: Dash
      Track listing: Football freaks (part 1) -- Football freaks (part 2)